♪You are my forever love I swear♪
♪Love and hate entangle us♪
♪I saw you in countless glances♪
♪Never want to part again in this life♪
[Circle of Love]
[Episode 5]
Hongye, what are you doing here?
Who do you think is here?
You…
You can't resist it
and carry on another man so quickly.
Someone set me up.
Don't pretend you don't know who it is.
Why should I believe you?
Then I'll show you
who is shouting "Catch the thief" so loudly?
Please don't.
Be gentle.
Get out!
Go, come on.
Come on, go.
Now you see clearly
the true color of your fiancée.
Do you think you're better than her?
At least I won't harm others actively.
Once you've used me, you want to leave.
I'm helping you.
You deliberately let others see us.
Didn't you want to tell others
your relationship with me?
So people here
don't dare to bully you anymore.
Thank you for cooperating with me.
Don't play tricks.
Remember.
You're just a lowly maid.
Hongye, are you tired?
This is Biluochun tea
that my father brought from Suzhou.
Try it.
It's getting cold.
How about I get you a jacket?
Hongye, I was wrong.
Don't go.
I was too impatient.
I'm afraid that Rumeng will steal you.
I'm afraid of losing you.
In the future,
at the Governor's Mansion,
I don't want to see this kind of thing again.
I dare not, Hongye.
I just love you too much.
All right.
If you don't let me go,
the list for your birthday party
will be soaked.
Do you prepare a birthday party for me?
Hongye, you are so sweet.
I'll go get a piece of paper
and write a new one.
Let's talk about the last thing.
No way. Half an hour?
Here.
[Happy Birthday to Zhou Jiaojiao]
OK. Thank you.
Come on.
Let's chat while drinking.
Mrs. Wang.
Miss Zhou and Mr. Xiao have arrived
Hongye,
are these all prepared by you for me?
Do you like them?
Yeah.
Go check if my father has come.
Thanks to you for the last order.
Otherwise, something bad will happen.
Mr. Zhou, please behave yourself.
How?
Why don't you teach me?
If you keep doing this, I won't be polite anymore.
What a hot girl!
You just need some discipline.
Mr. Zhou,
Jiaojiao is looking for you.
Can't you see I'm busy? Wait a moment.
Let me teach you how to be a person.
What do you think?
Father,
judging from her outfit,
she should be a maid from the Governor's Mansion.
What do you mean?
It's just a maid.
Do I have to obtain Xiao Hongye's permission?
Father, you misunderstood me.
I mean
Governor Xiao especially holds a birthday party
for Jiaojiao.
This place bustles with people.
In case someone sees
you are bullying a maid,
isn't that harmful to your honor
as a commander in chief?
Why are you still standing here?
The party has started.
Are you OK?
Thank you.
May I ask for your name, sir?
My surname is Zhou.
My name is Zhou Zichen.
May I have your name, miss?
My name is Rumeng.
Miss Rumeng,
you look somewhat familiar.
Maybe my looks are too ordinary.
Mr. Zhou, I will repay you in the future.
I still have work to do.
Excuse me.
Thank you, Mr. Zhou.
Zhou.
Huang.
Long time no see.
Your daughter is getting more and more beautiful.
Thank you.
Your wife is more charming.
Father.
What are you doing?
Mr. Zhou.
Hongye.
How is the dance hall case going?
There are already some clues.
We need further investigations.
Take it seriously.
Never slack off.
You would rather kill a thousand by mistake
not let one person go.
Please rest at ease.
Father, today is my birthday.
Can you talk about
official affairs another day?
OK.
We don't take about official affairs today.
I have a gift for you.
What is it?
Hello, everyone.
Today is my daughter's birthday.
I have a gift for her.
This is the latest model of an automatic pistol.
It is the only one in the whole city.
Today I give it to my beloved daughter.
You carry it with you.
If anyone dares to bully you,
shoot him dead.
Jiaojiao,
it is too risky by doing this, isn't it?
How about changing…
My target is that apple,
not her head.
Let me teach you how to shoot.
Stand with your feet apart.
Keep your shoulders level.
Aim at the target.
Fire.
Hongye, look how scared she is.
Zichen,
you haven't given me my gift yet.
Jiaojiao, this is the gift I prepared for you.
Hongye, does it look good?
Yes, it does.
Do you like it?
Yes, I like it.
Be careful.
Rumeng! Rumeng!
Doctor!
Call the doctor.
Rumeng, hang in there.
Doctor! Doctor!
Hold on, Rumeng.
Rumen!
♪Like the quietly approaching moon♪
♪The pure, bright moonlight falling into the lake♪
♪Like a flying butterfly in spring♪
♪Making my heart flutter♪
♪Just a glance with you in the sea of people♪
♪I swear I will love you forever♪
♪Tattoo a maple leaf on the shoulder♪
♪Keep you in my heart for the rest of my life♪
♪Years of love and hate entanglement♪